gosale.com 2016-03-05

# GoSale.com Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy   
---  
GoSale.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting GoSale.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.  
1\. Collecting of Information  
(a) Information You Give Us. We collect personally identifiable information when you provide it to us, such as when you contact us through the GoSale.com website, when you subscribe for an e-mail newsletter or when you register to use certain services. This information is used to reply to a specific request or to notify you if subscribed to the price alert service. We might receive information about you from other sources such as reviews and add it to our records.

(b) Traffic or Clickstream Data. Data about traffic and usage is not personally identifying or identifiable, and is not supplemented or combined with personally identifying or identifiable information. GoSale.com may share information it collects with certain selected third parties, but only in aggregated, anonymous form. The most common use for such data is to share information with with an advertiser regarding the number of people who viewed a certain product or page on our website. GoSale.com also collects information regarding use of the site by observing browser functions and the pages users access. This information is typically used in determining errors, inconsistencies, or problems with GoSale.com and our servers to better design the site for our users. 

(c) Cookies. GoSale.com implements the use of cookies for GoSale member verification. Members have the ability to post product reviews, merchant reviews, as well as the option to sign up for our special deal newsletter and pricing alert service.  
  
2\. Sharing of Information  
Information about our customers is an important for us to conduct and improve our services. However, we are not in the business of selling personal information to others and only share such information as described below.  
(a) Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control: GoSale.com provides a service to our users to purchase of products from our affiliated businesses. Information with these businesses is shared in the form of click-through streams (see 1b).  
(b) Protection of GoSale.com and Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of GoSale.com, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.  
(c) Business Transfers. In the event of a business transaction involving GoSale.com, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that GoSale.com or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets. (d) With Your Consent: Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.   
3\. Links to Other Sites  
GoSale.com contains links to other web sites. GoSale.com not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these sites. If you have concerns about how other web sites collect and use information about you, make sure to read that site's own privacy policy.   
4\. Contacting the Web Site  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:  
Per Ola Persson  
GoSale.com  
PO Box 2614  
Bangor, ME 04402
